Prentiss Taylor
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1885-1991, undated, Series 10:; (Box 3-21, OV 22; 18.0 linear feet; Reels 5913-5935)
  - Robert Jackson & Company, 1966 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 187)
  - Alice Rice Jaffe, 1934-1986, (22 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 189-1307)
  - Kristian Jakobsen, 1959 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1309-1310)
  - Macgill James, 1957 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1312-1314)
  - Mitchell Jamieson, 1944-1982, (3 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1316-1378)
  - Benjamin L. Jamison, 1954 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1380)
  - Josephine January, 1953 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1382-1383)
  - Gladys Jardine, 1975 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1385-1386)
  - Jefferson County Historical Society, 1960 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1388)
  - Frank R. Jelleff, 1946-1961 (Box 10, Reel 5922, Frame 1390-1417)
  - Marie Jenkins, 1960 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 13-16)
  - Gladys Jenkyns, 1960 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 18-20)
  - Ida Jervis, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 22)
  - Jewish Community Center, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 24)
  - Garnet Jex, 1979 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 26)
  - Harold Joachim, 1974 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 28)
  - Estella Taylor Johnson (Mrs. Horace W. Johnson; "Aunt Stella"), 1933-1978, (5 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 30-235)
  - Hall Johnson Negro Choir, 1931 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 237-238)
  - Johnston, Lemon, & Company, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 240-247)
  - Mrs. C. H. Jolls, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 249-250)
  - Helen Lyon Jones, 1945 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 252-259)
  - Lois Mailou Jones, 1948-1979 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 261-270)
  - Preston Jones, 1979 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 272)
  - June 1 Gallery, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 274-350)
  - Frances Jurkowitz, 1975 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 352)
  - Mae and Irving Jurow, 1986 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 354)
  - Betsy K., 1964-1983 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 356-365)
  - Wathen Tyler Kackley, 1956-1986 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 367-417)
  - Virginia and Sheffield Kagy, 1965, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 419-423)
  - Dorothy and Lloyd Kahn, 1968-1976 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 425-436)
  - Jacob Kainen, 1949-1984, (9 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 438-581)
  - Yumiko Kakimizu, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 583-593)
  - Fannie Kallivas, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 595)
  - Henry Kalmus, 1982 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 597)
  - Florence W. Kane, 1952 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 599-601)
  - Theodora Kane, 1956 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 603)
  - Hike Kaplan (Mrs. Robert Kaplan), 1966-1980 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 605-612)
  - Benjamin Karpman, 1962 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 614-615)
  - Bess Karrick, undated (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 617)
  - Hilda Katz, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 619-626)
  - Elizabeth Hazen Kaul, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 628-641)
  - Katharine Keck, 1948-1955 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 643-646)
  - Myrtle Keeney, 1953-1960 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 648-655)
  - George Keiser, 1956 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 657)
  - Kellaway Publishing Company, 1976 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 659)
  - Bruce Kellner, 1980-1986, (4 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 661-898)
  - H. and G. Kelly, 1953 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 900-901)
  - Isabella Stuart Kelly, 1956 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 903-908)
  - John B. Kelly, Jr. 1985 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 910)
  - Richard Hay Kenah, 1982 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 912)
  - Isabelle V. Kendig, 1949 (Box 10, Reel 5923, Frame 914)
  - Kennedy Galleries (see also Albert Reese), 1946-1980, (5 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 917-1047)
  - Dorothy Kent, 1935 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1049-1050)
  - Hugh Kepets, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1052-1054)
  - Sophie Kepner, 1925 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1056-1057)
  - Irvin Kerlan, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1059-1096)
  - Barbara Davis Kerne, 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1098-1099)
  - Harrison Kerr, 1932 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1101)
  - Jeanne Kerr, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1103-1104)
  - Peter Kerr, 1957 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1106)
  - Mr. Kibler, 1950 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1108)
  - Charlotte Stuart Kimball, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1110-1111)
  - Eve King, 1963 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1113)
  - Fay Ball King, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1115)
  - Mrs. Milton King, 1945 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1117)
  - Lee King, 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1119-1120)
  - Louise King, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1122-1128)
  - Lucius and Peggy Kingman, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1130-1136)
  - Marion Kingsbury, 1964-1978 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1138-1143)
  - George Kinsey, 1927 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1145)
  - Robert Kipniss, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1147-1152)
  - Emily Kiracofe?, 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1154-1155)
  - Kirby Lithographic Company, 1953 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1157)
  - Edward M. Kirk, 1964 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1159)
  - Madaline Kirker, 1951 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1161-1163)
  - Robert Kirkpatrick, 1961 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1165-1166)
  - Scott Kirkpatrick, 1953 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1168)
  - Richard Kirsten, 1955-1977 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1170-1222)
  - Ki-Wives, 1954 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1224-1226)
  - Samuel Klaus, 1963 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1228)
  - Elmer and Eleanor Klein, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1230)
  - Morris and Gertrude Kleinerman, 1981 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1232)
  - Henry J. Knight, 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1234)
  - Robert P. Knight, 1954 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1236)
  - Mary Knollenberg, 1946-1955 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1238-1250)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, 1929 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1252)
  - Kodak Processing Laboratory, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1254-1260)
  - Henry Koerner, 1973 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1262)
  - Misch Kohn, 1961 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1264-1269)
  - Oskar Kokoschka, 1980 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1271)
  - Marie Koontz, 1976 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1273)
  - Alice Graemme Korff, 1938-1975 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1275-1279)
  - Paull and Jean Kovachi?, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1281)
  - June and Norman Kraeft, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1283-1288)
  - Elaine Kramer, 1982 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1290-1317)
  - Edith Kranck?, 1959 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1319-1320)
  - Margaret Graham Kranking, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1322)
  - Heinrich Kraus, undated (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1324)
  - Bill Krause, 1951 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1326)
  - Doris Kreindler, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1328-1340)
  - Teruaki Kuyama, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1342-1356)
  - Hanna Kwiatkowska, 1980 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1358)
  - Denis L., 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1360-1361)
  - Sam L., 1929-1933 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1363-1371)
  - Odessa LaFont, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1373-1379)
  - Joseph Lambert, 1976 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1381-1382)
  - Margaret I. Lamont, 1933 (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1384-1385)
  - Armin Landeck, 1934-1988, (2 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5923, Frame 1387-1434)
  - Armin Landeck, 1934-1988, (4 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 13-98)
  - Marchal Landren, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 100-101)
  - Landmark Center, 1967 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 103)
  - Lois Landreth, 1962 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 107)
  - Landscape Club of Washington, D.C., 1945-1950 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 109-115)
  - Octave Landuyt, 1960 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 117-118)
  - Lois Langhorne, 1950-1975, (11 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 120-406)
  - Tadeusz Lapinski, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 408-431)
  - Eugene Larkin, 1961 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 433-435)
  - Mauricio Lasansky, 1956 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 437-458)
  - Muriel Laskoff, 1943 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 460-462)
  - Dorothy Lathrop, 1929-1956 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 464-487)
  - Henry A. Latimer & Son, 1979 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 489-490)
  - Basil La Trobe-Bateman, 1955 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 492)
  - Father Lauck, 1956 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 494-496)
  - Nancy Lauderbaugh, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 498-502)
  - Adelaide C. Law, 1960 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 504-506)
  - Lawrence (Family) Curry, 1962 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 508)
  - Fern Lawrence, 1953 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 510-511)
  - Jacob Lawrence, 1950 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 513-515)
  - John Lawrence, 1946 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 517-521)
  - Edna Lazaron, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 523-527)
  - Pietro Lazzari, 1946-1979, (2 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 529-576)
  - Zigmond Lebensohn, 1945-1986 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 578-631)
  - William P. Lecky, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 633-638)
  - Rita Leff, 1973 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 640-656)
  - Lotte Lehmann, 1976 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 658)
  - Chester Leich, 1930-1978 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 660-704)
  - Cora and Harold Leich, 1961-1981 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 706-708)
  - Josephine "Joeen" Leich and Clarence Leich, 1942-1960, (5 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 710-877)
  - John Foster Leich and Jean Ferriss Leich, 1957-1981 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 879-919)
  - Marcella Leich, 1960 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 921-922)
  - Martin Leich, 1920-1983, (3 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 924-1028)
  - Robert M. Leich, 1939-1983 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 1030-1069)
  - Roland and Constance Leich, 1932-1982, (6 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 1071-1300)
  - Walter Leich, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 1302-1304)
  - Howard Leigh, 1984 (Box 11, Reel 5924, Frame 1306-1308)
  - Clare Leighton, 1956-1977 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1311-1314)
  - Lottie Lenn, 1950-1975 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1316-1327)
  - Abram Lerner, 1984 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1329)
  - "Letters to the Editor," 1933-1951 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1331-1345)
  - Harold Leventhal, 1946 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1347)
  - Levy, 1933? (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1349)
  - Adele Lewis, 1962 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1351-1353)
  - Jo Ann Lewis, 1976-1991 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1355-1358)
  - John Chapman Lewis, 1949 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1360)
  - Martin Lewis, 1978 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1362-1366)
  - Nolan Lewis, 1979 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1368)
  - R. E. Lewis, Inc., 1965 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1370-1371)
  - Rae T. Lewis, 1978-1986 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1373-1398)
  - Robert Lewis, 1944-1950 (Box 12, Reel 5924, Frame 1400-1416)
  - Jay Leyda, 1932-1957 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 13-25)
  - Library of Congress, 1944-1986, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 27-230)
  - Life Magazine, 1947 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 232-233)
  - Mary Lilly, 1978 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 235-236)
  - Jean Lindsey, 1922 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 238)
  - Fred Linton, 1963 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 240)
  - Charlie Locke, 1934-1946 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 242-244)
  - Florence Locknane, 1953 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 246)
  - Eileen Loder, 1950 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 248-249)
  - John M. Lofton, 1948 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 251-256)
  - Polly Logan, 1973 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 258-259)
  - Ralph Logan, 1972 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 261)
  - Rosemary Long, 1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 263-264)
  - Anita Loos, 1969-1981 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 266-271)
  - Lord's Flower Shop, 1983 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 273)
  - Rose S. Lorivin, 1949 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 275-276)
  - Calder Loth, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 278-282)
  - Lo Turco Francesca, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 284-293)
  - Loudoun Sketch Club, 1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 295-307)
  - Amy Loveman, 1929 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 309)
  - James M. Lowe, 1948 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 311-315)
  - Marvin Lowe, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 317-326)
  - Loraine Lowry, 1961 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 328-329)
  - Julius I. Lowy, 1947-1951 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 331-340)
  - Louis Lozowick, 1959-1977 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 342-349)
  - Harry H. Lunn (Graphics International, Ltd.), 1946-1983 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 351-390)
  - Frances F. Lyon, 1959 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 392)
  - Rowland Lyon, 1954-1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 394-406)
  - Arthur Lyons, 1926-1927 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 408-411)
  - Leonard Lyons, 1976 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 413)
  - Colin M., 1930 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 415-424)
  - Else M., 1964-1979 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 426-437)
  - Mary and Mel M., 1954-1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 439-441)
  - Jessie MacBride, 1925-1939 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 443-456)
  - Alice Foote MacDougall, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 458)
  - MacDowell Colony Fellows, 1929-1984, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 460-604)
  - Mary Mace, 1945 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 606-607)
  - Margaret Macelfatrick, 1957 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 609-615)
  - John MacIver, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 617-618)
  - Florence Mackay, 1948 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 620-621)
  - Wilda Mackenzie, 1953-1971 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 623-637)
  - Elizabeth MacKinstry, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 639-652)
  - Kenneth MacLean, 1953 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 654-655)
  - Frank Gair Macomber Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 657-658)
  - Noel Macy, 1955-1961 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 660-665)
  - Magruder's, Inc., 1949-1951 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 667-671)
  - Charles Mahoney, 1967 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 673)
  - Felix E. Mahony, 1928 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 675-678)
  - Kay Malone, 1946-1948 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 680-684)
  - Eleanor L. Manchester, 1953-1974 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 686-711)
  - Ernest Manfred, 1948 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 713)
  - Manhattan Storage and Warehouse Company, 1939 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 715-720)
  - Alexis Many?, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 722-723)
  - S. L. Margolies, 1951 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 725)
  - Maria's Restaurant, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 727-732)
  - Herman Maril, 1949-1983 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 734-746)
  - Isabella Banks Markell, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 748)
  - Marmon Trading Company, 1960 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 750)
  - Mildred Maroney, 1941-1977 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 752-760)
  - Anne Steele Marsh, 1968-1976 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 762-770)
  - Reginald Marsh, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 772-773)
  - Hans Herbert Martin, 1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 775-776)
  - Una Martin, 1954 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 778-779)
  - Frederic Marvin, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 781-785)
  - Maryland Institute College of Art, 1974-1981 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 787-791)
  - Maryland School of Art and Design, 1972 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 793-799)
  - Mason Fine Prints, 1976-1983 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 801-807)
  - Russell Mason, 1964 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 809-810)
  - May Massee, 1928 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 812)
  - B. Matheson, 1980 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 814-815)
  - Ann Maun, 1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 817)
  - Leonard Maurer, 1966-1981, (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 819-863)
  - Isabelle "Cookie Belle" May and Viola May, 1915-1931 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 865-875)
  - Corrie McCallum, 1971 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 877-878)
  - Joseph McCarthy, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 880-881)
  - Mrs. Howard Mayer, 1962 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 883)
  - Mayo Clinic, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 885)
  - A. Hyatt Mayor, 1980 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 887-888)
  - John McAndrew, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 890)
  - Thomas D. McAvoy, 1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 892)
  - Bernard J. McCall?, 1947 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 894-895)
  - Parke McClellan, 1949-1959 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 897-928)
  - Rose McClendon, 1932 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 930)
  - A. T. McClintock, 1962 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 932)
  - Frank McClure, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 934-940)
  - Virginia T. McCormick, 1946-1957 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 942-944)
  - J. McDonald, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 946-948)
  - Anne Genevieve McEldowney, 1953-1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 950-952)
  - Cameron McGraw, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 954-961)
  - Hal McIntosh, 1957 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 963)
  - Ellen McL., 1960-1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 965-973)
  - Robert E. McLaughlin, 1959-1978 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 975-982)
  - Colin McPhee, 1982 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 984)
  - Jonathan Meader, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 986-991)
  - Leila Mechlin, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 993-995)
  - Eugene Mecikalski, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 997-1000)
  - Medical Society of the District of Columbia, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1002-1010)
  - Morley G. Melden, 1981 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1012)
  - Evelyn E. Mellon, 1982 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1014)
  - John Melver, 1953 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1016-1017)
  - Eric Menke, 1979 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1019)
  - Menninger Foundation, 1959 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1021)
  - Mental Hygiene Society of Greater Baltimore, 1956 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1023-1028)
  - Meridian House, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1030-1031)
  - Mesa Verde National Park, 1959-1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1033-1035)
  - F. H. Meserve, 1938 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1037-1038)
  - Jack Metherell, 1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1040)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1950-1974 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1042-1044)
  - Metropolitan Opera, 1984 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1046-1051)
  - Meyer Foundation, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1053-1054)
  - Herman Mezger, 1965 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1056)
  - Miami Graphics Biennial, 1978 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1058-1061)
  - University of Michigan Museum of Art, 1984 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1063-1064)
  - Ann Miciatto, 1976 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1066)
  - Mickelson's, Inc., 1970-1984 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1068-1073)
  - Frank Milan, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1075)
  - Hirst Milhollen, undated (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1077)
  - Jerome Milkman, 1937 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1079)
  - Beveridge Miller, 1979 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1081)
  - Burr Miller, 1967 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1083-1086)
  - George C. Miller & Son, Inc., 1941-1978, (2 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1088-1169)
  - Edward Millman, 1946 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1171)
  - Kenneth and Mildred Mills, 1953 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1173)
  - Daniel Millsaps, 1961 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1175)
  - Mary A. Milton, 1965 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1177-1178)
  - Peter W. Milton, 1966-1982 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1180-1220)
  - Wang Ming, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1222-1225)
  - Mint Museum, 1948-1952 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1227-1249)
  - George Miyasaki, 1966 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1251-1252)
  - Elizabeth Mongan, 1955 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1254-1258)
  - Peter Monkton, 1944-1948, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1260-1363)
  - Ruth Gove Monohon, 1961-1983 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1365-1413)
  - Montgomery College, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1415-1416)
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, Department of Recreation, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1418-1426)
  - Montgomery County Fair, 1961 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1428-1429)
  - Benson B. Moore, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1431-1433)
  - Hope Bissland Moore, 1950 (Box 12, Reel 5925, Frame 1435-1437)
  - Keiko Hiratsuka Moore, 1963-1980 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 13-40)
  - L. Carroll Moore?, 1956 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 42-43)
  - Marjorie Morawetz, 1933-1936 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 45-55)
  - Herman More, 1968 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 57)
  - Charlotte Morehouse, undated (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 59-60)
  - Anne Morgan, 1938 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 62)
  - Ruth Morgan, 1952 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 64)
  - Whitney Morgan, 1940-1942 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 66-87)
  - Alice B. Morse, undated (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 89)
  - Peter Morse, 1966 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 91)
  - Ren Morse, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 93-96)
  - Robert T. Morse, 1964 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 98-99)
  - Wayne Morse, 1948 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 101)
  - David Morton, 1975 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 103-104)
  - Mory's Association, Inc., 1941 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 106)
  - August Mosca, undated (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 108)
  - Harold Moulton, 1929 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 110-130)
  - Hildy and Hans Mueller, 1976 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 132-133)
  - Municipal Museum of the City of Baltimore, 1937-1954 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 135-138)
  - Walter Murch, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 140-141)
  - Alice Murphy, 1926 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 143-144)
  - Donn B. Murphy, undated (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 146)
  - James Patric Murphy, 1944 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 148)
  - Mr. Murrow, 1954 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 150)
  - Museum of the City of New York, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 152-158)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1934-1981 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 160-193)
  - George F. Muth Company, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 195-198)
  - Ruth N.?, 1968 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 200-201)
  - Michael Nadel, 1977 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 203-204)
  - Lee and Bob Naiman, 1952 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 206-207)
  - Edith Namias, 1961 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 209-210)
  - The Nation, 1933 (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 212)
  - National Academy of Design, 1946-1984, (3 folders) (Box 12, Reel 5926, Frame 214-360)
  - National Academy of Design, 1946-1984, (8 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 362-931)
  - National Association for Mental Health, 1950 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 933)
  - National Association for Music Therapy, 1953 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 935-937)
  - National Cathedral School, 1945 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 939)
  - National Collection of Fine Arts, 1956-1981 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 941-1022)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1956-1986 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1024-1051)
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1957 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1053-1056)
  - National League of American Pen Women, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1058-1103)
  - National Museum of American Art, 1978-1986 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1105-1149)
  - National Portrait Gallery, 1984 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1151-1157)
  - National Presbyterian Church, 1960 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1159-1160)
  - National Rehabilitation Association, 1954 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1162-1165)
  - National Soap Sculpture Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1167-1173)
  - National Society of Arts and Letters, 1950 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1175-1177)
  - National Symphony Orchestra, 1954-1985 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1179-1182)
  - Dorothy Natsui, 1955 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1184-1186)
  - Department of the Navy, 1957 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1188-1195)
  - Neighborhood Art Show, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1197-1207)
  - David Nelson, 1947-1962 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1209-1218)
  - Nelson Gallery of Art, 1960 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1220)
  - Nelson-Whitehead Paper Corporation, 1959 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1222)
  - Jackson Lee Nesbitt, 1984 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1224-1225)
  - Newbury Frame Shop, 1944 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1227)
  - Mike and Milena Newlin, 1967 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1229-1232)
  - Kathryn Newlon, 1979 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1234-1238)
  - New Mexico Museum of Art, 1959 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1240)
  - University of New Mexico, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1242)
  - New School for Social Research, undated (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1251)
  - New Virginia Review, undated (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1253)
  - New York City Opera, 1976 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1255)
  - New York Public Library, 1948-1981 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1257-1269)
  - New York State Theatre, 1976 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1271)
  - John Jacob Niles, 1980 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1273)
  - Beverly Noble, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1275-1278)